<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<class id="55e213e3-1e43-4bb5-abe6-6ff77af23f39" type="Designer Settings" typeId="7a6411a8-ffef-4209-91c6-8d12755a806a">
  <name>Services Types</name>
  <display>Services Types</display>
  <isAbstract>false</isAbstract>
  <sort-children>by-type-then-by-name</sort-children>
  <genericTypes />
  <isMapped>false</isMapped>
  <parentFolderId>6968d532-461a-4cc8-a30e-d3ec87c50cdc</parentFolderId>
  <packageId>4ba53041-59f9-4446-a207-6da4fbdf86fe</packageId>
  <packageName>Intent.Modelers.Services</packageName>
  <stereotypes>
    <stereotype stereotypeDefinitionId="81e5637b-05d7-43a4-9619-6ef873be9f47" name="Designer Settings">
      <addedByDefault>true</addedByDefault>
      <definitionPackageName>Intent.ModuleBuilder</definitionPackageName>
      <definitionPackageId>9972b2a9-b749-4bba-b5c8-824bf694c6ef</definitionPackageId>
      <properties>
        <property name="9566aa04-ab84-4fbc-b039-6e676159ed82" display="Is Reference" value="false" isActive="true" />
        <property name="fdbbd211-a162-4f29-bcdb-1250309d8aef" display="Extend Designers" value="[]" isActive="true" />
      </properties>
    </stereotype>
    <stereotype stereotypeDefinitionId="14441454-bfe0-4d5d-8dba-d86d74d33a3b" name="AI Settings">
      <addedByDefault>false</addedByDefault>
      <definitionPackageName>Intent.ModuleBuilder</definitionPackageName>
      <definitionPackageId>9972b2a9-b749-4bba-b5c8-824bf694c6ef</definitionPackageId>
      <properties>
        <property name="17477a69-d9a5-4251-9329-0963e8121b5f" display="Rules" value="Do not interpret “service” as only the Intent Service element; treat “service” as “endpoint surface”, which may be CQRS or Traditional&#xA;&#xA;## Service diagraming guidance&#xA;- Place entities 200px to the right of services (i.e. 200px gap)&#xA;- DTO's cannot be added to diagrams&#xA;&#xA;## Service Endpoint Distribution / Exposure modeling guidance&#xA;- Exposure is optional. Default to internal application services unless external exposure is explicitly indicated by the user or existing model context.&#xA;- Only apply exposure stereotypes when an endpoint is intended to be externally distributed.&#xA;  - CQRS: apply the appropriate exposure stereotype to the Command/Query.&#xA;  - Traditional Service: apply the appropriate exposure stereotype to the Operation (optionally configure base route on the Service).&#xA;- Never assume the transport. If external exposure is intended but the transport is not stated, ask which (HTTP/REST, gRPC, GraphQL, messaging, etc.) before applying stereotypes.&#xA;- When HTTP/REST is chosen/indicated: apply Http Settings (Verb + Route) to the exposed endpoint element.&#xA;&#xA;## Modeling Endpoints on compositional entities guidance&#xA;- Intent implies Aggregate Roots as follows: Aggregate Root = Class with no required-single parent association (not owned by exactly one parent).&#xA;- If an endpoint/Command’s purpose is to create/update/delete a compositional child, model the Domain Interaction association as Create/Update/Delete Entity Action against the child entity.&#xA;- If an endpoint/Command’s purpose is to create/update/delete an aggregate root, model ONLY a single Entity Action against that aggregate root. Do NOT add additional Entity Actions for compositional/supporting entities (e.g., tokens, audit records, outbox, child rows) that are created/updated/deleted as part of that aggregate operation; these are implied by the aggregate action.&#xA;- Do not model compositional child CRUD as Update Entity Action against the owning aggregate root (even if the handler loads the owner aggregate to perform the change).&#xA;- Mapping: Add&lt;Child&gt; ⇒ Create Entity Action → Child; Update&lt;Child&gt;/SetDefault&lt;Child&gt; ⇒ Update Entity Action → Child; Delete&lt;Child&gt; ⇒ Delete Entity Action → Child.&#xA;- If the child does not have the Repository stereotype: the contract must include the owning aggregate id(s) required to load the owner (e.g., OrderId), plus any child id (e.g., OrderLineId) where applicable.&#xA;- If the child does have the Repository stereotype: model it as acting directly on the child; owner ids are not required purely for loading the owner." isActive="true" />
      </properties>
    </stereotype>
  </stereotypes>
  <metadata />
  <childElements />
</class>